# Normunds Lastovka,

Address

Home: 1 Victoria Court,

Mansfield,

Nottinghamshire,

NG18 5SP

Mobile number: 07411793988

Email address: <a href="mailto:normundsnon@gmail.com">normundsnon@gmail.com</a>

### **Profile**

I am a passionate, creative and highly qualified education professional with 8 years' experience in a broad range of settings. I am a goal driven, customer focussed individual with proven ability to produce excellent results both for the business and customers. I have excellent interpersonal skills, ability work in team, effectively and am pro-active in my approach. These skills have enabled me to have a strong positive impact on service delivery, self-education and high potential.

## **Areas of Expertise**

 $Computer\ systems,\ Networks,\ Hardware\ and\ software\ maintenance,\ Work\ with\ different\ types\ of\ software$ 

Security officer, Driver

Club photographer

Telecommunication Field Engineer, Smart Property System Maintenance, Customer Service

### **Main Skills**

- $\circ \quad Telecommunications \ systems \\$
- o Customer Service
- o Computer and computer system maintenance
- o Hardware and Software installing and maintenance
- o Network and network system maintenance
- o Office equipment installation and maintenance
- o Windows, Linux, Mac OS
- o Photoshop and CorelDraw
- o Photo shooting
- o Key holder
- o CCTV
- o Close protection
- o Driving
- o Language Skills English, Russian, Latvian

## **Employment Summary**

Enterprise House, Gala Bank Business Park, Galashiels TD1 1PR

Qube GB (Qube Engineering LIMITED ) – Telecommunication Field Engineer November 2016 – August 2019

Grenville Court, Britwell Road, Brunham, Bucks, SL1 8DF MASH services LTD, Security Guard – Groundsman August 2015 – November 2016

19 Totteridge Common, London, N20 8LR, Private Security January 2014 – August 2015

15 Berkeley Street, Mayfair, London, W1J 8DY Funky Buddha Club photographer February 2012 – January 2015

21-22 Wrotham Business Park, Wrotham Park, Barnet, Hertfordshire, EN5 4SZ Evolution Emergency Response Limited, Security officer May 2011 - January 2014

Latvia, Daugavpils, PRO LINE D Junior Computer System Technician, June 2009 – Jul 2011

### **Education**

Jaunaglonas Professional Secondary School (College) 2010 Computer System Technician

The Tech Partnership 2018 Advanced Level in Apprenticeship in IT, Software,

Web & Telecoms Professionals

Pearson 2018 English Level 2

Mathematics Level 2

ITC Level 2

BTEC level 3 in Professional Competence for IT and

**Telecoms Professionals** 

BTEC level 3 in ITC systems and Principles

### Courses

SIA course 2011 Door Supervisor

PQMS Training 2017 Level 2 Broadband Technicians

(City&Guilds)

NFCE 2017 Level 2 in Equality and Diversity

#### **Additional**

Full UK Driving Licence

#### References

References are available upon request